<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Document xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
    <Name>Let Us Praise the Lord</Name>
    <Uuid>28c70071-ce5e-4add-aa5c-d093acfb2785</Uuid>
    <Translations>
        <Translation Language="English">
            <Stanza>Let us praise the Lord, for with glory, He was glorified. He ascended into the heavens, and sent us the Paraclete, the Spirit of Truth. Amen alleluia.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>He made the two become one, that is, the heaven and the earth. He ascended into the heavens, and sent us the Paraclete, the Spirit of Truth. Amen alleluia.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>Come all you nations, to worship Jesus Christ. He ascended into the heavens, and sent us the Paraclete, the Spirit of Truth. Amen alleluia.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>This is God our Savior, and the Lord of all flesh. He ascended into the heavens, and sent us the Paraclete, the Spirit of Truth. Amen alleluia.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>Three in one and one in three, the Father, the Son, and the Holy Spirit, the Spirit of Truth. Amen alleluia.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>A perfect Trinity, triangled and unified, that is the Father the Son, and the Holy Spirit, the Spirit of Truth. Amen Alleluia.</Stanza>
        </Translation>
        <Translation Language="Greek">
            <Stanza>̀‍Ⲁⲥⲱⲙⲉⲛ ⲧⲱ Ⲕⲩⲣⲓⲱ: ⲉⲛⲇⲟⲝⲱⲥ ⲅⲁⲣ ⲇⲉ ⲇⲟⲝⲁⲥⲑⲉ. ̀‍Ⲁⲛⲉⲗⲑⲱⲛ ⲓⲥ ⲟⲩⲣⲁⲛⲟⲥ: ⲁⲝⲓⲧⲟⲛ Ⲡⲁⲣⲁⲕⲗⲏⲧⲟⲛ: ⲧⲟ ̀‍Ⲡⲛⲉⲩⲙⲁ ⲧⲏⲥ ̀‍ⲁⲗⲏⲑⲓⲁⲥ. ̀‍Ⲁⲙⲏⲛ ̅‍ⲁ̅‍ⲗ.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>Ⲧⲟⲩⲥ ⲇⲩ̀‍ⲟ ̀‍ⲕⲧⲓⲥⲁⲥ ⲓⲥ ̀‍ⲉⲛⲁ: ⲧⲟⲛ ⲟⲩⲣⲁⲛⲟⲛ ⲕⲉ ⲧⲏⲛ ⲅⲏⲛ. ̀‍Ⲁⲛⲉⲗⲑⲱⲛ ⲓⲥ ⲟⲩⲣⲁⲛⲟⲥ: ⲁⲝⲓⲧⲟⲛ Ⲡⲁⲣⲁⲕⲗⲏⲧⲟⲛ: ⲧⲟ ̀‍Ⲡⲛⲉⲩⲙⲁ ⲧⲏⲥ ̀‍ⲁⲗⲏⲑⲓⲁⲥ. ̀‍Ⲁⲙⲏⲛ ̅‍ⲁ̅‍ⲗ.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>Ⲇⲉⲩⲧⲉ ⲡⲁⲛⲧⲉⲥ ̀‍ⲓⲗⲁ̀‍ⲓ: ̀‍ⲡⲣⲟⲥⲕⲩⲛⲏ ⲥⲱⲙⲉⲛ Ⲓⲏⲥⲟⲩ Ⲭⲣⲓⲥⲧⲱ. ̀‍Ⲁⲛⲉⲗⲑⲱⲛ ⲓⲥ ⲟⲩⲣⲁⲛⲟⲥ: ⲁⲝⲓⲧⲟⲛ Ⲡⲁⲣⲁⲕⲗⲏⲧⲟⲛ: ⲧⲟ ̀‍Ⲡⲛⲉⲩⲙⲁ ⲧⲏⲥ ̀‍ⲁⲗⲏⲑⲓⲁⲥ. ̀‍Ⲁⲙⲏⲛ ̅‍ⲁ̅‍ⲗ.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>Ⲟⲩⲧⲟⲥ ⲉⲥⲧⲓⲛ ̀‍ⲟ Ⲑⲉⲟⲥ ̀‍ⲟ Ⲥⲱⲧⲏⲣ ̀‍ⲏⲙⲱⲛ: ⲕⲉ Ⲕⲩⲣⲓⲟⲥ ⲡⲁⲥⲓⲥ ⲥⲁⲣⲕⲟⲥ. ̀‍Ⲁⲛⲉⲗⲑⲱⲛ ⲓⲥ ⲟⲩⲣⲁⲛⲟⲥ: ⲁⲝⲓⲧⲟⲛ Ⲡⲁⲣⲁⲕⲗⲏⲧⲟⲛ: ⲧⲟ ̀‍Ⲡⲛⲉⲩⲙⲁ ⲧⲏⲥ ̀‍ⲁⲗⲏⲑⲓⲁⲥ. ̀‍Ⲁⲙⲏⲛ ̅‍ⲁ̅‍ⲗ.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>Ⲧⲣⲓⲁⲥⲉⲛ ⲙⲟⲛⲁⲇⲓ: ⲕⲉ ⲙⲟⲛⲁⲥⲉⲛ ̀‍ⲧⲣⲓⲁⲇⲓ: ̀‍ⲟ Ⲡⲁⲧⲏⲣ ⲕⲉ ̀‍ⲟ Ⲩⲓⲟⲥ: ⲕⲉ ⲧⲟ ̀‍Ⲁⲅⲓⲟⲛ ̀‍Ⲡⲛⲉⲩⲙⲁ: ⲧⲟ ̀‍Ⲡⲛⲉⲩⲙⲁ ⲧⲏⲥ ̀‍ⲁⲗⲏⲑⲓⲁⲥ: ̀‍ⲁⲙⲏⲛ ̅‍ⲁ̅‍ⲗ.</Stanza>
            <Stanza></Stanza>
        </Translation>
        <Translation Key="CopticTranslation" Language="Coptic" Font="CS Avva Shenouda">
            <Stanza>Marenhwc `e`P[oic@ je qen ou`wou gar au[i`wou. Afsenaf `e`pswi `enivyou`i@ afouwrp nan `mPiparaklyton@ Pi`pneuma `nte ]me;myi. `Amyn =a=l.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>Pentafer pi`cnau `nouai@ `ete vai pe `tve nem `pkahi. Afsenaf `e`pswi `enivyou`i@ afouwrp nan `mPiparaklyton@ Pi`pneuma `nte ]me;myi. `Amyn =a=l.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>`Amwini nilaoc tyrou@ `ntenouwst `nIycouc Pi`,rictoc. Afsenaf `e`pswi `enivyou`i@ afouwrp nan `mPiparaklyton@ Pi`pneuma `nte ]me;myi. `Amyn =a=l.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>Vai pe `Vnou] Pencwtyr@ ouoh `P[oic `ncarx niben. Afsenaf `e`pswi `enivyou`i@ afouwrp nan `mPiparaklyton@ Pi`pneuma `nte ]me;myi. `Amyn =a=l.</Stanza>
            <Stanza></Stanza>
            <Stanza>Ou`triac ecjyk `ebol@ ecoi `nsomt ecoi `nouai@ `ete vai pe `Viwt nem `Psyri@ nem Pi`pneuma e;ouab@ Pi`pneuma `nte ]me;myi@ `amyn =a=l.</Stanza>
        </Translation>
        <Translation Source="\ipa{\def{CopticTranslation}}"/>
        <Translation Language="Spanish">
            <Stanza>Alabemos al Señor, porque el del la gloria, fue glorificado. El ascendió a los cielos, y nos ha enviado el Paraclete. Espíritu de la verdad el Consolador. Amen, Alleluia.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>El hizo los dos en uno, que es el cielo y la tierra. El ascendió a los cielos, y nos ha enviado el Paraclete. Espíritu de la verdad el Consolador. Amen, Alleluia.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>Vienen todas las naciones, para adorar a Jesucristo. El ascendió a los cielos, y nos ha enviado el Paraclete. Espíritu de la verdad el Consolador. Amen, Alleluia.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>Esto es Dios, nuestro Salvador, y el Señor de todos al mundo. El ascendió a los cielos, y nos ha enviado el Paraclete. Espíritu de la verdad el Consolador. Amen, Alleluia.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>Trinidad en uno y uno en la trinidad, el Padre el Hijo y el Espíritu Santo. Espíritu de la verdad, el Consolador. Amen, Alleluia.</Stanza>
            <Stanza></Stanza>
        </Translation>
        <Translation Language="Italian">
            <Stanza>Lodiamo il signore perche con la gloria si glorificò. Sali nell'alto dei cieli e ci mandò il Paraclito. Lo Spirito della verità il consolatore Amen Alleluia.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>Fece i due in uno, cioè il cielo e la terra. Sali nell'alto dei cieli e ci mandò il Paraclito. Lo Spirito della verità il consolatore Amen Alleluia.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>Venite o tutti i popoli per inginocchirci a Gesù Cristo. Sali nell'alto dei cieli e ci mandò il Paraclito. Lo Spirito della verità il consolatore Amen Alleluia.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>Questo è Dio nostro salvatore, e Dio di ogni corpo. Sali nell'alto dei cieli e ci mandò il Paraclito. Lo Spirito della verità il consolatore Amen Alleluia.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>Trinità in uno, e uno in trinità, il Padre, il Figlio e lo Spirito Santo. Lo Spirito della verità il consolatore Amen Alleluia. Sali nell'alto dei cieli e ci mandò il Paraclito. Lo Spirito della verità il consolatore Amen Alleluia.</Stanza>
            <Stanza></Stanza>
        </Translation>
        <Translation Language="Dutch">
            <Stanza>Laten wij de Heer prijzen, want Hij is met de glorie verheerlijkt. Hij is opgevaren ten hemel en zond tot ons de Parakliet, Geest der Waarheid de Trooster, Amen Halleluja.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>Hij heeft de twee tot één gemaakt, dit zijn de hemel en de aarde. Hij is opgevaren ten hemel en zond tot ons de Parakliet, Geest der Waarheid de Trooster, Amen Halleluja.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>Komt alle volkeren, om te knielen voor Jezus Christus. Hij is opgevaren ten hemel en zond tot ons de Parakliet, Geest der Waarheid de Trooster, Amen Halleluja.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>Dit is God onze Verlosser, en de Heer van iedereen. Hij is opgevaren ten hemel en zond tot ons de Parakliet, Geest der Waarheid de Trooster, Amen Halleluja.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>De Drie zijn Eén, en de Ene is Drie: de Vader en de Zoon, en de Heilige Geest, de Geest der Waarheid, Amen Halleluja.</Stanza>
            <Stanza></Stanza>
        </Translation>
        <Translation Language="Arabic">
            <Stanza>فلنسبح الرب، لأنه بالمجد تمجد. صعد إلى أعلى السموات، وأرسل لنا البارقليط، روح الحق المعزي. آمين هلليلويا</Stanza>
            <Stanza>جعل الإثنين واحداً، أي السماء والأرض</Stanza>
            <Stanza>تعالوا يا جميع الشعوب، لنسجد ليسوع المسيح</Stanza>
            <Stanza>هذا هو الله مخلصنا، ورب كل جسد</Stanza>
            <Stanza>ثالوث في واحد وواحد في ثالوث، الآب والإبن والروح القدس، روح الحق المعزي. آمين هلليلويا.</Stanza>
            <Stanza>ثالوث كامل مثلث وموحد الذي هو الآب والابن والروح القدس، روح الحق. أمين هلليلويا.</Stanza>
        </Translation>
    </Translations>
</Document>